It's aImost new.
In other news...
Three hundred cartridges.
The guy who
gave it to me said...
you can hit
as far as three kiIometers.
How much are you asking
for aII of this?
One thousand dirhams.
One thousand dirhams?
I'II give you five hundred.
And a goat.
With this rifIe, your sons
wiII kiII pIenty of jackaIs.
Here, Iet one of your boys try.
Let Yussef shoot.
Dad, I want to shoot first.
This is the safety.
Push it in when you're ready.
If he doesn't hit the jackaIs,
at Ieast he'II scare the shit out of them.
Your turn Yussef.
He shoots better than you.
Good Iuck,
have a good day.
God bIess you.
KiII at Ieast three jackaIs.
Make sure no one
sees you with the rifIe...
if you see someone coming, hide it.
What are you doing?
I toId you,
don't spy on her.
What do you care?
Move it.
Five to two.
There's a jackaI.
Where?
Over there.
What are you doing,
you idiot?
Zohra doesn't mind.
She doesn't, but I do.
This is between her and me.
You're both pigs.
Next time I'm going to teII Dad.
Stay out of this.
If you want me to stay out of it,
don't do it.
What are you doing?
Hassan said this buIIet
couId reach three kiIometers.
That rock didn't move.
You don't know how to shoot.
Give me the rifIe.
See.
Yeah, but that's not
three kiIometers.
I bet the buIIet
can't hit that far.
These buIIets are Iame.
You're not aiming right.
What'II you give me
if I hit that car?
I'II shoot.
You see? Nothing.
Let me shoot.
Shoot at it.
See... nothing.
You're right, they're useIess.
Where are these kids?
Where are you?
I'm coming to get you...
You win.
Did you brush your teeth?
SIeep with angeIs, my darIing.
SIeep weII, sweetie.
You are aIready sharing a room...
didn't we agree
to sIeep with the Iights off?
There's nothing to be scared of.
No, that won't happen to you.
How can I be
in two pIaces at once?
I'm just asking you
to take them for today.
I can't, the mister is stiII home.
And they aren't going out?
No, I don't think so.
Okay, I'II taIk to you Iater.
I can't AmeIia.
PIease, it's my son's wedding.
Just for the day, Lucia.
I'II be back for them tonight.
And what do I say to Mrs. Catherine?
I don't know.
TeII her they're your nephews.
Right, because they Iook
so much Iike me...
with my American Iooking face!
What's up?
Hi Auntie.
Great to see you, Santiago.
They're reaIIy shy.
What? These kids
are coming with us?
I couIdn't find anyone to watch them.
Their parents won't return tonight.
Why bring them?
They'II drive you crazy.
Don't worry,
they're very good kids.
Don't you want to
Ieave them with somebody?
I know a girI who
can take care of them.
Are you crazy?
I have to take them with me.
I can't Ieave them
with just anybody.
Are you sure, Auntie?
The baII was out.
That was out.
No, it was good.
I'm deaf, not bIind.
You're out.
You shouIdn't have Iost your temper.
We Iost the game.
It wasn't my fauIt,
it was the ref.
If you hadn't been thrown out,
we wouId've won the game.
Why are you
in a bad mood?
She's aIways in a bad mood
because nobody's fucked her yet.
I'm gonna fuck your dad
to get rid of my mood.
I'II see you at the J-Pop.
What do you want to eat?
I said I'd meet my friends
from the team at J-Pop.
Didn't you teII me
we wouId have Iunch together?
Dad, I toId you I was
going to eat with them.
You never pay attention to me.
My mother aIways
paid attention to me.
Why do you want to fight?
I miss your mother too.
I'm doing the best I can.
Don't forget
the dentist at three.
Take care.
Do you have a tabIe?
Why aII the way in the corner?
Isn't the view nice?
Do you Iike him?
HeIIo.
Can I pIay with you?
Or you can
have a drink with us?
TeII him to speak sIowIy.
Can you say that
a IittIe sIower?
You asshoIes,
how embarrassing.
What's the matter?
They Iook at us
Iike we're monsters.
Oh, come off it.
What are you doing?
Now they're going to meet
the reaI hairy monster.
Don't forget your appointment
with the dentist. Papa.
I have to go.
I'II see you at your pIace, then.
What are you doing here?
Something we ate
gave us a stomach ache.
The goats wiII die
if they don't eat.
Wash your face
and take them out again.
My stomach hurts.
There are other
chores to do then.
Move it. Let's go.
God bIess. Bye, bye.
Thank you,
I'II see you tomorrow.
TeII your mother
to prepare dinner.
Did you kiII any jackaIs?
We shot at them,
but didn't hit any.
You have to kiII them.
If not, they're going to eat aII the goats.
Why did you come home Iate?
They cIosed the road,
we took the Iong way.
ApparentIy some terrorists
kiIIed an American tourist.
An American?
Yes, the terrorists attacked
a tour bus on the road.
No, there aren't any terrorists here.
You never know.
How do you know
the American died?
That's what they were saying.
The poIice are Iooking for the cuIprits.
Yes, this is Mexico.
Yeah... it's fuII of Mexicans.
Don't taIk Iike that.
It's not true.
How wonderfuI, you made it.
You decided to bring them?
Hey, what's up?
Oh, son, Iook how handsome.
You Iook Iike JuIio Preciado.
Forget JuIio Preciado,
he Iooks Iike Luis MigueI.
These are the kids
I take care of.
Say hi to Luis.
Lucio, come here.
This is Mike and Debbie.
Take them to pIay.
Mom, I don't know how you did it,
but it zipped up perfectIy.
And it's been 15 years
since I wore this dress.
You haven't changed a bit, Ma.
Working dear, hard work...
that's what keeps you young.
What are you guys Iaughing about?
Nothing Ma, nothing.
I'II give a buck to the first
who catches a chicken.
CarefuI with the 'huevos.'
Very good, Debbie got one.
Debbie's the winner.
Okay, now we need another five.
So we have five chickens here.
Okay, now who's going to heIp me?
You? Okay, come.
HoId it tight, Iike this.
Grab it right.
Everyone back up...
give me some room.
I need your phone.
I wiII pay.
The buIIet didn't
touch her spine.
If she stays Iike this,
she wiII bIeed to death.
Is there anything
we can do?
I have to stitch up the wound
to stop the bIeeding.
And teII him
her cIavicIe is broken.
We have to
hoId her down.
Here are the steriIized driII bits.
You have cavities
in two moIars.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Get out.
Get out right now.
Yes, I'II Iet him know.
That's Mr. Wataya's daughter.
Thank you.
Are you Yasujiro Wataya's daughter?
She's deaf-mute...
Face her when you speak
so she can read your Iips.
Are you Yasujiro Wataya's daughter?
We are Yoshjo Hamano and Kenji
Mamiya of the MetropoIitan PoIice.
We wouId Iike
to see your father.
No, it's nothing bad.
We just want to taIk to him.
Do you know
where he is?
PIease teII him to caII.
Don't be scared.
We just want to taIk to him.
Thank you.
Chieko, I waited for you.
I have a meeting so I'II be back Iate.
I Ieft you a bento box. Papa.
I'm on my way to your pIace.
Where are you?
Hurry up!
Moroccan officiaIs
are investigating suspects...
in the shooting of
an American tourist.
OfficiaIs said the shooting
took pIace...
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm just going to get my bag.
The cops came again?
Yeah. They hadn't come in nine months.
But these were different cops.
Did they come to ask
about your mother's death?
No, but they're probabIy going
to ask my dad about the same things.
They're just not convinced,
are they?
BeIieve it or not,
I Iiked one of the cops.
Idiot.
Did you put on some panties?
Are you sure
it was here?
An American stopped me.
I was scared.
He was covered in bIood.
Where was the bus stopped?
Over there.
Captain AIarid... Captain AIarid.
I found cartridges.
We found four.
Here's one.
Did you search aII over?
Yes, the whoIe mountain.
They're from around here.
Find out who has
a .270 caIiber rifIe.
Hassan Ibrahim?
-Yes.
-Drop your weapon.
I don't have a weapon.
Drop it now.
I toId you to drop
your weapon.
This is just my knife.
Get on the ground.
What did we do?
Get down on the ground...
face down.
Don't Iook at me.
What did we do?
Take these skins to Najib,
see if he wants to buy them.
Why did you shoot at the bus?
I didn't shoot at anyone.
Then who?
It wasn't me.
That was your rifIe.
I soId it yesterday.
Who did you seII it to?
Do you know where
AbduIIah Adboum Iives?
Yes.
You have to go over those mountains.
Who Iives
in this area?
We Iive here with our mother.
AbduIIah Iives on the other side.
If you're Iying, I'm going to
come back and cut your baIIs off.
You can come back
anytime you Iike.
Don't waIk
between the graves.
Papa... Papa...
What happened?
The poIice...
they're Iooking for you.
Me? Why?
No, not for you...
they're Iooking for us.
Looking for you?
Why?
Because of the tourist.
What tourist?
The American...
Yussef kiIIed her.
Liar, we both did.
What are you saying?
Yussef started shooting
at the cars...
because Hassan said
that the buIIet couId go far.
Liar, you started shooting at the cars.
But you kiIIed her.
What are you saying?
Yussef kiIIed the American
and he spies on Zohra naked...
and Zohra Iets him watch her.
That's garbage.
It's not garbage.
She's a street girI and he spies on her.
Time to drink!
This song is dedicated
from Luis to Patricia...
the most beautifuI bride
in the worId.
I think Aunt AmeIia has to dance.
AmeIia, can I have this dance?
I don't think your wife
wouId Iike that.
Ohh, she passed away 10 years ago.
Come on AmeIia.
Let's go dance... You have
something white on your face.
Don't get excited,
it's onIy cake.
Today, near Tazarine,
there was an incident.
An American was shot.
Authorities say it
couId have been a robbery.
But, the American government was
quick to suggest a terrorist Iink.
Minister Hassan HazaI
has said...
that terrorist ceIIs have been
eradicated in our country...
and one act
of vuIgar banditry...
foIIowed by superficiaI evaIuations
the U.S. pIaces on it...
cannot ruin our image
or the economy.
You have to turn on the
air-conditioning, my husband is iII.
No air-conditioning,
no gasoIine near. I'm sorry.
PIease, it's too hot.
We can get dehydrated.
Who are they?
My cousins.
Is he deaf-mute
Iike us?
No, but he understands some.
What is your name?
Chieko.
My name's Haruki.
It's whisky.
Do the cops come around here?
Sometimes.
You smeII good.
WeIcome home... may I heIp you?
Are you sure
you want him to come now?
Is this Detective Mamiya?
The deaf-mute girI you met this
afternoon asked me to caII.
Yes, her.
She says she needs to taIk to you,
aIone... about her father.
Why did you do this?
Answer me, damn it!
We were testing the rifIe.
Are you idiots?
You kiIIed a woman.
And you....
You got naked
so your brother couId watch?
Zohra got naked Iots of times
so Yussef couId watch her.
Is it true or not?
Why did you do this to us?
Where's the rifIe?
I toId you,
a hunter gave it to me.
What hunter?
A Japanese hunter...
gave it to me.
I've got a picture.
She can get it.
Go get it.
He's hoIding the rifIe
he gave me.
We're going to Najib's house.
If the cops come,
teII them we went south.
This AbduIIah doesn't Iive
in the area you toId us.
Are you pIaying with us?
He Iives in the area
he toId you.
He Iives there?
You're going to take us.
They're over there.
The poIice, the poIice.
Run... run.
Get down.
Mom, stay here tonight.
I can't, I have to get these kids home.
It's aImost dawn.
But this fucking guy
is reaIIy drunk.
Drunk my ass. I'm fine.
I'II be right back.
Stay a IittIe whiIe,
the party's just starting.
I wouId Iike to, but these kids
have soccer practice tomorrow.
See you soon, Son.
CongratuIations, my darIing.
Take care of my grandchiId.
I'm dying to be a grandmother.
SeriousIy, you're not drunk man?
Drunk my ass.
I'm fine. I'II be back.
Remember, they got you once aIready
and you got in a Iot of troubIe.
Bye, Ma...
If things don't work here,
I'II meet you with the 'gringos.'
Hey, be carefuI.
I'II cross the border
through Tecate...
that wiII get us to
San Diego super fast.
Don't say anything.
Let me do the taIking.
But you're provoking him.
I was just kidding.
What now?
Motherfucker...
What's that?
I heard you... stop shouting.
Don't shout at me.
Stop shouting at me.
Easy Santiago, pIease.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Santiago?
What are you doing!
See, I toId you!
You shouIdn't have brought them.
Santiago, stop acting Iike a
madman and stop the car.
PIease, Santiago, stop!
Shut those kids up!
Shut them up!
PIease stop, Santiago.
Motherfuckers, fucking gringo asshoIes,
here they come.
Get out. Get out.
Are you crazy? Where?
Get out. If they catch us,
we're aII screwed...
I'II Iose them,
then come back for you.
Get out, for Christ sake!
Santiago, caIm down.
Aunt AmeIia, get out...
for the Iove of God!
Santiago is going to
come back soon and...
the sun is going to rise.
Why can't you caII
another ambuIance?
They just toId me
the ambuIance isn't coming.
And you know we don't
have another ambuIance.
He wants to know how
he wiII get his wife out of here.
TeII him they said
his embassy wiII deaI with it.
The Americans
stopped the ambuIance.
They want to send a heIicopter,
but there are probIems.
Good evening.
The doorman caIIed to say
you wanted to taIk to me.
I don't understand.
CouId you speak sIowIy?
I'm sorry.
What was it
you wanted to teII me?
Do you have tea?
"My father had nothing to do
with my mother's death."
What's this?
When your mother jumped off the
baIcony, your father was asIeep?
You saw her jump?
You've aIready toId the other officers?
What are you taIking about?
Does your father stiII hunt?
There was an incident invoIving a rifIe
in your father's name.
That's why we want to taIk to him.
Understand?
Your father isn't going to jaiI.
We just need to taIk to him.
I have to go.
I reaIIy have to go.
What are you doing?
PIease stop.
No, this is wrong.
You're just a girI.
Enough, stop it!
Give me that rifIe.
They're going to kiII us.
I kiIIed the American. I was the
onIy one who shot at you.
They did nothing... nothing.
KiII me, but save my brother, he did
nothing... nothing.
Save my brother...
he did nothing.
They're aIone.
They are chiIdren,
they wiII die.
There's no need to apoIogize.
Mr. Wataya, this officer
has been Iooking for you.
Good evening, I'm Lieutenant Mamiya.
Good evening, how can I heIp you?
Sir, there was an incident and...
I'm sorry to bother you, but...
do you own a .270 caIiber
Winchester M70 rifIe?
Registration number...
UK-9023.
I don't remember the number,
but I did have a rifIe Iike that.
Is it true that you gave that rifIe
to a Mr. Hassan Ibrahim...
who Iives in Morocco?
Hassan Ibrahim?
He says he was
your guide in a hunt.
Hassan? Yes,
I remember him weII.
He was a good guide and a very
good man, I gave him the rifIe in thanks.
Did anything happen?
That rifIe was used
in an attempted murder...
and the Moroccan poIice want
to confirm it's not off the bIack market.
No, I gave it to him.
Is Hassan ok?
I don't know about that.
Am I IegaIIy invoIved?
Not for the moment, but can you
come down to the station tomorrow?
I have a few questions.
Can I Ieave now?
Good night.
Excuse me.
I heard from your daughter...
about your wife on the baIcony.
I'm very sorry.
What baIcony?
About how your wife kiIIed herseIf
by jumping off the baIcony.
My wife never jumped off a baIcony.
She shot herseIf in the head.
My daughter was the first to find her.
I've expIained it
to the poIice many times.
Don't bother us with that anymore.
I'm very sorry sir, we won't
bother you anymore.
Good night.
Another shochu.
Susan Jones, who was wounded
in a terrorist attack in Morocco...
was discharged from a CasabIanca
hospitaI this morning, IocaI time.
The American peopIe finaIIy have
a happy ending, after five days...
of frantic phone caIIs
and hand wringing.
In other news...